(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-05T02:27:01.308068",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
みゃーみゃーみゃんこlogyで
myah myah myah cology
人類みゃ？とれびゃ～ん！
mankind mya? träs bie~n!
たとえば磁石　砂の中には
for example, magnets within the sand
宇宙人が地球支店にてteatime
the aliens have their teatime at their branch on Earth
ちっちゃいと不便だ　おっきいの出してよ
it's inconvenient being small, send out the big ones
戦艦大和だれか動かして
someone move Battleship Yamato!
ダバダバダー　牛乳飲んで
drink milk
シャバダバダ　早めに就寝
go to sleep early
ダバダバダー　大人手きっとこっそり変身
adults certainly transform in secret
怪人ダァー放っときゃいいじゃん
Monster Dashing, better to leave him alone!
総統ダー　指令はなにー？
supreme leader, what's your order?
制服ダー　漢字がへんだー！
uniform, your letters are weird!
かーめーはーめー波ー
kamehameha!
冥土　冥土　メイドのみやげ
underworld, underworld, a maid's souvenir
そりゃもうshangri-laのそっくりさん
that's already a dead ringer for Shangri-La
タイムマシン手作りしました
I built a homemade time machine
時を歩く少女追い越した
I overtook the girl who walks through time
退屈　退屈　体育座りで
boredom, boredom, sitting with my knees up
膝の匂いを嗅ぐと陶酔感
I feel giddy from sniffing the scent of my knees
タイムマシン一人乗りでしょ
the time machine only seats one, right?
歴史塗り替えたら【総集編！】
if you repaint history, it's the summary!
君はつまり感情論ばかりで事をさらに複雑にしている
in short, you make things even more complicated by only following your emotions
君はすでに達者なのと言えば済むか完璧な馬鹿だ
you're already like a philosopher, or a complete idiot
うまうまうましかしか？
horse horse ho-, deer deer deer?
まうめうめうまかしかしか！
shore shore es, reed reed reed!
それなりにそれなりなり鳥肌？
for being what it is, goosebumps?
愛ゆえに頭ゆんんで恋ゆえに心ゆかんで
because of love, my head is swimming; because of romance, my heart is twisted
さみだれのそらとどろにほほとぎす
and there's a cuckoo in the rumbling sky of early summer rain
巻いて巻いて巻いていたら要らない
I don't need to wind it up
無電らんらんらんらんそう　なった
that's right, I've got wireless LAN, la la la la
森よ森よ森のどんぐり拾い集めたあと虫わくよ
forest, after I gathered up acorns, the insects would stir
年は歳を追い越してゆく
the years are overtaking my age
それもあたりまえの業界談
that's also natural business talk
表裏はウラがオモテでおもて意外腹黒さが最小値
for the front and back, the back is the front and malice is the lowliest
みゃーみゃーみゃんこlogyで
myah myah myah cology
人類みゃ？とれびゃ～ん！
mankind mya? träs bie~n!
にゃーにゃーにゃんこlogyで
meow meow kitty ology
生類みゃ？にゃにゃにゃにゃ～ん！
creatures meow? mew meow mew me~ow!
なによりもきみがすきだとしよりよりもきみがすきだ
I love you more than anything, I love you even when you're old
あいしてるきもちわるいさわるな
I love you, that sounds sick, don't touch me!
あいしなさいむちゃくちゃゆうなあいしませうやさしくゆうな
please love me, don't force yourself to say it tenderly!
あいしあおうこっちをみるなつづきは？つづかない！
let's love each other, don't look at me, there's no more!
ソリティュードソリティュードsorry, sorry, solitude.
solitude, solitude, sorry, sorry, solitude
ゆれる日差しと君の笑顔に会う
Flickering sunlight and meeting your smile,
例えばそんな事の為僕は生きている
For example, I live for things like that.
正しさのベクトルなんて簡単に変わる
The vector of correctness changes so easily.
愛は偉大ななる原動力だって
Love is a great driving force,
声を殺し泣いた君を抱きしめた
I held you as you cried, stifling your voice.
心の中なら慄えるものなど何もない
There's nothing to tremble at in your heart.
ほら今宵エデンの片隅で
See, tonight, in a corner of Eden,
愛の行方探しましょう
Let's search for the destination of love.
形がないものならば
If it's something without a shape,
いつも感じていればいい
It's fine if we always feel it.
今宵エデンの片隅で
Tonight, in a corner of Eden,
淡い心つなぎましょう
Let's connect our faint hearts.
世界がスパークとけていくまでに
Until the world melts away into sparks.
安息の為に争うことなんて
Whether fighting for peace is necessary
必要かどうか僕にはわからないことだ
I don't really know.
優しさの意味だって人によって違う
Even the meaning of kindness differs by person,
僕は君に許されていたい
I want to be forgiven by you.
多くを望めばいつも満たされないもの
Wanting too much leaves you never satisfied,
空っぽの心で欲しがるばかりじゃやりきれない
You can't get by just wanting with an empty heart.
ねぇ 今宵エデンの片隅で
Hey, tonight in a corner of Eden,
僕にも愛を下さいと
Saying "Please give me love too,"
打ち明けるよ今がチャンス
Let's confess, now is the chance.
付け入る隙を逃さない
Don't miss the opening to take advantage.
今宵エデンの片隅で
Tonight, in a corner of Eden,
快楽へと突き落として
Throw me into pleasure,
眠れぬ夜はクレイジーラージデイズ
Sleepless nights are crazy large days.
終焉はもうすぐ来るよ
The end is coming soon.
遠い今日を撃ち粉々にしてサイレン
Smashing the distant today into pieces, siren.
今宵エデンの片隅で
Tonight, in a corner of Eden,
愛の行方探しましょう
Let's search for the destination of love.
形がないものならば
If it's something without a shape,
いつも感じていればいい
It's fine if we always feel it.
今宵エデンの片隅で
Tonight, in a corner of Eden,
淡い心つなぎましょう
Let's connect our faint hearts.
世界がスパークとけていくまでに
Until the world melts away into sparks.
今宵エデンの片隅で
Tonight, in a corner of Eden,
僕にも愛を下さいと
Saying "Please give me love too,"
打ち明けるよ今がチャンス
Let's confess, now is the chance.
付け入る隙を逃さない
Don't miss the opening to take advantage.
今宵エデンの片隅で
Tonight, in a corner of Eden,
快楽へと突き落として
Throw me into pleasure,
眠れぬ夜はクレイジーラージ2
Sleepless nights are crazy large 2.
世界がスパークとけていくまでに
Until the world melts away into sparks...
眠れぬ夜はクレイジーラージ2デイズ
Sleepless nights are crazy large 2 days.
はーい、ということで始まえました！
Hi everyone, and so we've started!
いや1発目から疲れる楽曲だったね本当に。
Man, what an exhausting song right from the first track.
いや本当につかれた！
Man, I'm really tired!
えー、本日はですね、ホロライブゲーマーズ結成記念ライブ2024ということで
Um, today is the Hololive Gamers Anniversary Live 2024,
ハッシュタグがございますので、ぜひ感想をつぶやいてください！
So please tweet out your impressions with the hashtag!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you very much!
今回のステージなんですけど、みんな後ろのこの、ビコビコさ気づいた？
About this stage, did everyone notice the blinking in the back?
おおー！ビコビコ！
Whoa! Blinking!
我々のこう、ビコビコ動くらしいんで、ちょっとコロナにやってもらおうか。
Apparently ours blink and move, so let's have Korone try it.
わあ… ささやか。
Woah... how subtle.
わあ！すっごい！耳が動いてる。
Whoa! Amazing! Her ears are moving.
すごいねこれね！ねえ！
This is amazing, right! Right!
いやすごいね、後ろも見て。ゲーマーズ入り口。オープニングも可愛かったね！
Man, it's amazing. Look in the back too. Gamers Entrance. The opening was cute too!
確かに、このロゴね、使うんだね、まだね。
True, we're still using this logo, huh.
そうだよ、まだ使っていくんだよ、このロゴは。オオカミかな、オオカミのやつ。
Yeah, we're gonna keep using this logo. Is it a wolf? A wolf one.
すすきさいっぱいいるもんね。本当みんな来てくれてありがとう！
There are tons of fans. Thanks everyone for coming!
本当みんなありがとうございます！めちゃめちゃ嬉しいよ！
Really, thank you everyone! We're so happy!
今日誕生日な人おめでとう！それをおめでとうだ！
Happy birthday to anyone whose birthday is today! Congrats on that!
さて今回、結成記念ライブということで説明をお願いします！
Now, since this is an anniversary live, please explain!
えーっとですね、ホロライブゲーマーズはみんなが同じような時期にデビューしたのではなくてですね
Um, Hololive Gamers didn't all debut around the same time,
フブキが6月に1期生としてデビュー
Fubuki debuted as 1st gen in June,
そのあとにウチが12月に、フブキと一緒にホロライブゲーマーズとして最初二人でウチだけソロデビュー
And then I debuted in December alongside Fubuki, initially as two for Hololive Gamers, but just me solo debut
そのあとに4月にオカコロがデビューして、今の4人の形になったということで
And then Okakoro debuted in April, forming the four of us we have now,
一応結成の12月を、結成記念とさせていただいたということで
So we designated December as our anniversary,
聞いてなかったでしょ？
You hadn't heard of that, right?
聞いてた！だから12月にミオシャが来たからそれで結成して記念ライブだって話ね
We heard it! That's why Miosha came in December, so we formed up and had an anniversary live.
よかった、ということでそういうことになっております。
Good, so that's how it is.
この後もまだまだみんな歌うのでな、体力大丈夫ぞ？
Everyone's gonna keep singing after this, is your stamina okay?
あ、ゆびゆび！はやーい！
Ah, yubi yubi! So fast!
あ、これ回復して回復して！回復した？
Heal this, heal this! Did it heal?
めっちゃ疲れた。
I'm so tired.
なんでだよ！
Why are you saying that?!
疲れてるって言ったじゃん！
You said you were tired!
なんでだよ！
Why?!
ま、でもね。今回なんですけども、なんとね、コンセプトを決めまして、我々。
Well, but for this time, we've decided on a concept.
はい！はい！
Yes! Yes!
メンバーの歌ってほしい曲をあみだくじで決めて、その人がねプロデュースした楽曲を歌ってもらうという。
Deciding requested songs via lottery, and having them sung.
プロデュース形式のライブとなっております。
It's a producer-style live concert.
おもしろい、おもしろい。で、今回ね、あの、誰がどの曲をやるとか話し合わずにですね、
Interesting! Without discussing who does which song,
突然あみだくじを用意しまして。
we suddenly prepared a lottery.
じゃあ、どのあみだがいいか引いてね。
So, draw which lottery you want.
で、結果的にうちがあみだくじで決めさせていただいたという。
And as a result, we let us decide via lottery.
そうそうそうそう。
That's right, yeah.
というわけで、まずは1曲目は！でででででで…誰だ？
So, first, the first song is... ddd... Who is it?
はーい！
Yay!
めっちゃ疲れてるって言ったけど、大丈夫か、おかゆん？
You said you were super tired, are you okay, Okayu?
でもね、うん。
But, you know, yeah.
頑張ります！
I'll do my best!
で、この曲はね、ぼくの大好きな妹が選んでくれたわけです！
And this song was chosen by my beloved little sister!
妹じゃねえだよ！お前がプロデュースしてって言ったんだろ！
I'm not your little sister! You asked me to produce it!
え、嘘だろ！？
Eh, really?!
どんな思い出でちょっと選んだの？
What kind of memories did you choose it with?
いやこれおかゆ、この楽曲を聞いたときに、まずおかゆに歌ってほしいなって思った楽曲で。
Well, when I heard this song, I wanted Okayu to sing it.
で、こんこんずっと持ってて、で、今回のこのライブやるってので、あ、これちょうどいい、おかゆに歌ってもらおうって。
I kept holding onto it for this live, thinking it's perfect.
いや、歌詞はね、すごいおかゆっぽいんだよ。
The lyrics are really Okayu-like.
え、そうなの！？
Eh, really?!
なので、すごい可愛い楽曲となってますので、じゃあみんな準備しますか？
So it's a super cute track, everyone ready?
はい！はい！
Yes! Yes!
おっけー、よしよし。いくぞいくぞ。ほら、おかゆも、みんな準備して。
Okay, let's go. Get ready, everyone.
ありえない幻想
Impossible illusions,
あふれだす妄想
overflowing delusions.
君以外全部
Everything except for you
いらないわ
I don't need at all.
幻想アスパルテーム
[Song: Mousou Aspartame]
作詞・作曲：picco
[Lyrics & Music: picco]
息をするように嘘ついても
Even if I lie as naturally as I breathe,
あたしやっぱいらない子？
am I still a useless girl after all?
こぼれ出しちゃった承認欲求
My overflowing desire for validation
もっとココロ満たしてよ
fills my heart even more.
アスパルテーム 甘い夢
Aspartame, a sweet dream.
あたしだけに愛をください あぁ もう無理
Give your love only to me... Ah, I can't take it.
まじむり こうして愛して 救済思考バグ
Seriously impossible, love me, salvation thought bug.
好きって言わせてよ？
Won't you make me say "I love you"?
ありえない幻想
Impossible illusions,
あふれだす妄想
overflowing delusions.
とまんない とまんない よくがちらばって
Unstoppable, unceasing desires scatter around.
求めてる愛情 隠してる恋情
Craving affection, hiding romantic feelings.
君以外全部
Everything except for you
いらないわ
I don't need at all.
誰のこと見てんの？
Who are you looking at?
こういうの好きなの？
Do you like this kind of thing?
DDとかガチでやめてください
Seriously, stop being an oshi-oshi fan of everyone.
かわいくなりたい！キラキラしてたい！
I want to be cute! I want to sparkle!
もっともっとガチで褒めてください
Seriously, praise me more and more!
泣いちゃう散々 開けちゃうシャンパン
Crying so much, popping champagne.
今夜も配信来てくれるよね？ね？
You'll come to the stream tonight too, right? Right?
独占させてよ 本音なんだよ
Let me monopolize you, I mean it.
もっともっとガチで推してください
Seriously support me more and more!
飲み過ぎ注意 オーバードーズ
Careful not to drink too much, overdose.
クラクラさせて いつだって
Make me dizzy, always.
あぁ もう無理 まじむり あがってさがって 救済思考バグ
Ah, no way, seriously no way, up and down, bug.
好きって言わせて？
Won't you let me say "I love you"?
噛み付いた衝動 戻れない焦燥
Bitten impulse, irreversible impatience.
たまんないミッドナイト 指が絡まって
Unbearable midnight, our fingers intertwine.
ときめいた表情 なにも言わないで
A heart-throbbing expression, don't say a word.
君だけがきっと 王子様
Surely only you are my prince.
ありえない幻想
Impossible illusions,
あふれだす妄想
overflowing delusions.
とまんない とまんない よくがちらばって
Unstoppable, unceasing desires scatter around.
求めてる愛情 隠してる恋情
Craving affection, hiding romantic feelings.
君以外全部
Everything except for you
いらないわ
I don't need at all.
あたしだけずっと 追いかけて！
Keep chasing only me!
もう待てないの
I can't wait anymore.
君以外全部
Everything except for you
いらないわ
I don't need at all.
はーい！「妄想アスパルテーム」歌わせていただきましたー！
Yay! I got to sing "Mousou Aspartame"!
かわいい！みた？
Cute! Did you see it?
めっちゃ可愛かったよ！
It was super cute!
いやなんか、あんまりさ、こんな可愛い曲歌うことないからさ。
Well, I rarely ever sing such cute songs.
もう、さっきさこのおかゆの衣装めっちゃ好きでさ。
I just loved Okayu's outfit right now.
え、本当？このスカートとかすごいすきすきだけど。ふぁふぁ。
Eh, really? I love this skirt so much. Fluffy.
結構ほら、ふぁふぁってするの。本当だ！かわいい！
Look, it's quite fluffy. Really! So cute!
なんか、そう、いろいろいるよ？
There are all sorts of them, you know?
あ、もしもし？あの、気しないで、あの。
Hello? Um, don't worry about that, um.
え？そう、
Eh? Is that so?
いいからいいから。
It's fine, it's fine.
わかった。
Got it.
いいからいいから。わかった。
It's fine, it's fine. Got it.
いや、本当にさ、この曲もめっちゃ、オカユめっちゃ合ってる感じしたけど、どうだった？この曲歌ってみて。
Man, really, this song seemed to fit Okayu so well, what did you think singing this song?
いや、確かに歌いやすかったけど、フブキPが
Well, it was certainly easy to sing, but Fubuki P...
こう僕のことよく見てくれてるから、こういうふうなことできるんだなと思って。
...watches over me so well, so I thought, "Ah, that's why we can do something like this."
あれ？なんかこの頭の中にコロスくんいる？
Huh? Is Korosu-kun inside this head?
違う違う違う！違う違う違う！違う違う違う！
No, no, no! No, no, no! No, no, no!
これあの、あれ？抱き枕じゃないから。
This is, um, what? It's not a body pillow.
あ、違う？あ、そう。
Ah, really? Ah, I see.
違うよ。
That's wrong.
なんかコロスくんの匂いしたような気がしたんだけど。
I felt like I smelled Korosu-kun for a second.
しないしないしないしない！ぜんぜんぜんぜんしないから！
Not at all, not at all! Not at all!
わかった。
Got it.
そう。もしもし？もしもし？はーい。うん。
I see. Hello? Hello? Hii. Yeah.
ちょっとね、あの、まあまあ。
Well, you know, um, oh well.
でもよかったね、すごい。
But it was great, really.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
嬉しいね、この曲選んでもらってね。
I'm so glad you chose this song for us.
次はさ、みおちゃんの番でしょ？
Next up is Mio-chan's turn, right?
ちょっと緊張しちゃうな。がんばってくるよ。
I'm getting a little nervous. I'll do my best!
僕がね、みおちゃんに歌ってほしい歌をプロデュースしました！プロデュースしてもらいました！
I produced the song I wanted Mio-chan to sing! I got it produced for me!
それこそみおちゃんも、歌うとめーーっちゃかっこいい系の人多いから。
Especially since Mio-chan has a lot of super cool songs when she sings.
そうだね、どっちかっていうとそうかも。
That's true, maybe so.
そう、今回はみおふぁんのみんなにめっちゃかわいいみおちゃんをお届けしたくて！
So, this version is to deliver a super cute Mio-chan to all the Miofans!
かなりアイドルみおを楽しんでいけ、いただけると思います！
I think you can really enjoy idol Mio!
かわいい、もうかわいいすでに。
Cute, already so cute.
ちょっと情報量すごいけどね、やっぱり。無視しきれないんだけど。
There's a lot of information to take in, though. I can't ignore it.
まあまあまあまあ。何やってるの？おいおいおい、いい加減にしなよ！
Come on now. What are you doing? Hey, cut it out!
怒られてる。
You're getting scolded.
はい。じゃあ、そろそろ、い、い、いっちゃう？ちょっと緊張してきたけど。
Alright. So, shall we get going soon? I'm getting a bit nervous though.
わかった。みおちゃんの心の準備ができてたらちょっと準備しに行きましょう。
Got it. If Mio-chan is mentally ready, let's go get ready.
はい。じゃあがんばって歌います！
Okay. Then I'll do my best and sing!
はい、がんばってね！
Yes, do your best!
邪魔邪魔！行って行って！
Out of the way! Go on!
もう一回こっち向いて
Look this way once more,
言いたいことがもっとあるから
'cause I have so much more to say to you.
もう一回こっち向いて
Look this way once more,
本気が揺れる 愛のFuture
where true feelings shake—love's future.
だからこっち向いて
So look this way,
まわれ地球 恋をのせて
spin, Earth, carrying my love along,
だからこっち向いて
so look this way—
偶然じゃない fanta future!
not by coincidence, fanta future!
私から誘う勇気をくださいと月を願うの
I wish upon the moon for the courage to invite you myself.
切ないところに魔法をかけてみましょう
Let's cast a spell over this bittersweet place—
未来への近道ね
a shortcut to the future!
甘くなれ 笑顔で君を溶けちゃえ
Become sweet, and melt you away with a smile!
今日の夜空を見つめ…ちょっと背伸びで
Gaze at tonight's night sky... stretching up a bit.
もう一回こっち向いて
Look this way once more,
言いたいことがもっとあるから
'cause I have so much more to say to you.
もう一回こっち向いて
Look this way once more,
本気が揺れる 愛のFuture
where true feelings shake—love's future.
だからこっち向いて
So look this way,
まわれ地球 恋をのせて
spin, Earth, carrying my love along,
だからこっち向いて
so look this way—
偶然じゃない fanta future!
not by coincidence, fanta future!
私だけ好きになってと大それた望み持ってる
I harbor the bold wish that you'll only fall in love with me.
慌てちゃいけない 魔法がゆっくり効いて
Don't panic, let the magic take effect slowly—
未来では仲良しね
we'll be close in the future!
かくなれ 身体は君とふわふわ
Grow light, and my body feels all fluffy with you!
今日の夜空を飛んで…遠い場所へと
Flying across tonight's night sky... toward a distant place.
ねえ ずっと会いたかった
Hey, I've always wanted to see you,
恋することが世界の平和
for falling in love is world peace.
ねえ ずっと会いたかった
Hey, I've always wanted to see you,
変えてみせる 愛でFuture
I'll show you I can change it with love's future.
だいすき 会いたかった
I love you, I wanted to see you—
まわる地球 恋する純情
spin, Earth, loving innocence.
だいすき 会いたかった
I love you, I wanted to see you—
何でもできる fanta future!
anything is possible, fanta future!
切ないところに 魔法をかけたら
Once we cast a spell over this bittersweet place,
ふたりで 遠い場所へと
the two of us will head to a distant place.
ねえ ずっと会いたかった
Hey, I've always wanted to see you,
恋することが世界の平和
for falling in love is world peace.
ねえ ずっと会いたかった
Hey, I've always wanted to see you,
変えてみせる 愛のFuture
I'll show you I can change it with love's future.
だいすき 会いたかった
I love you, I wanted to see you—
まわる地球 恋する純情
spin, Earth, loving innocence.
だいすき 会いたかった
I love you, I wanted to see you—
何でもできる fanta future!
anything is possible, fanta future!
ねぇ ずっと 会いたかった
Hey, I've always wanted to see you,
なんでもできるはずさ Future
I'm sure anything is possible, Future!
切ない心に 魔法をかけたら ふたりで
If we cast a spell on our aching hearts, together...
遠い場所へと
To a distant place!
ねぇ ずっと 会いたかった 恋することが 世界の平和
Hey, I've always wanted to see you. Loving you is world peace.
ねぇ ずっと 会いたかった 変えてみせる 愛で Future
Hey, I've always wanted to see you. I'll change it with love, Future!
だいすき 会いたかった まわる地球 恋する順序
I love you, I wanted to see you. The spinning Earth, the sequence of falling in love.
だいすき 会いたかった なんでもできるはずさ Future
I love you, I wanted to see you. I'm sure anything is possible, Future!
はいっ！どうでしたでしょうか！ファンダスティックフューチャー！
Yay! How was that? Fantastic Future!
よかった！よかった！ありがとー！耳すっごい効いててー！
It was great! Thank you so much! My ears were working super well!
よかったよみんな！かわいかった！
Everyone did great! It was so cute!
ありがとう！ありがとう！めっちゃかわいかったよ！
Thank you, thank you! It was super cute!
こうねも衣装変わってるね！ちょっと変えてみたの！
Korone's outfit changed too! I tried changing it a bit!
おおー！この衣装めっちゃかわいいんだよな！
Ohh! This outfit is super cute!
え？おーい！ え、なに？
Huh? Hey! Eh, what?
こねの衣装はまだいいの！ え、なんんで？歌をね！
Korone's outfit is fine for now! Eh, why? The song!
ちょっと感想聞かせてよ！どうだったどうだった歌ってみて！
Tell me your thoughts! How was it, how was it singing it?
えーと、うちはこの曲初めて歌ったんだけど、なんかね、あの、意外と歌いやすい肩？
Um, this was my first time singing this song, but you know, it was surprisingly easy to sing?
なんかおかゆは分かってんだなって。
Like Okayu understood it.
確かに！おかゆがね、プロデュースしたからね。そうそう！
True! Okayu produced it, after all. That's right!
よかった！いやそうなんだよ！いいじゃん部下二人も！
Good! Yeah, that's right. Your two subordinates are great too!
なんか言ってる！
You're saying something!
え？そうなの？なに？
Huh? Is that so? What?
え、なんかホロゲマズ結成記念ライブ2024がなんと、えーと、Xのトレンド1位になったそうです！
Eh, apparently the Hologamers Formation Anniversary Live 2024 reached #1 on X trends!
やったー！ありがとう！みんないっぱいつぶやいてくれて！
Yay! Thank you! Everyone tweeted so much!
今日敵が少なかったのかな？
Were there fewer enemies today?
敵って言うなよ！
Don't call them enemies!
ありがとう！Xで共に戦う仲間だろ！
Thank you! We're comrades fighting together on X!
確かに！やめろよ！
True! Cut it out!
よかった！嬉しいねなんかね！
Yay! I'm so happy!
いやね、そうだよ！嬉しい嬉しい！
Yeah, that's right! I'm so happy!
えーと、次のかねの曲はうちがプロデュースしました！
Um, I produced Korone's next song!
あのね、すごい難しかった！
You know, it was super difficult!
あ、難しかった？めちゃめちゃ難しかったよ！いっぱい練習したの。
Oh, was it difficult? It was super difficult! I practiced a lot.
だから不安！うちさ、好きな曲なんだけどね、
So I'm nervous! I mean, it's my favorite song, but...
いやもうね、こな！ってなって、めちゃめちゃ練習しました今日ののために。
Yeah, I was like "Korone!" and practiced so much for today.
いやあ、嬉しいな！絶対こなの声には絶対合うと思って選んだから。
Man, I'm so happy! I chose it because I knew it would definitely suit Korone's voice.
で、ちょっとリスナーさん聞いててね！聞いててね！楽しみにしててね！
So listeners, listen closely! Listen closely! Look forward to it!
じゃあこな、頑張って！うちちょっと
Okay Korone, do your best! I'm gonna...
頑張る！いってくるから！帰るから！
I'll do my best! I'm going! I'm going home!
わかった！行ってくる！
Got it! Have fun!
これ持って帰って、ちゃんと！
Take this back with you properly!
もういいの！もうさんざん自由にしたでしょ！もう帰るよ！声出すな！
That's enough! You've done whatever you wanted! I'm going home! Don't make noise!
帰るぞ！頑張ってね！ありがとう！
We're going home! Do your best! Thank you!
頑張る！
I'll do my best!
この混沌とした令和のインターネットを照らす一筋の光
A single ray of light illuminating this chaotic Reiwa internet,
電子の海を漂うオタクに笑顔を
bringing a smile to the otaku drifting in the electronic sea.
未来の平和をお約束 躁鬱だけどまかせとけ！インターネット・エンジェル ただいま降臨！
Promising peace for the future—I'm manic-depressive, but leave it to me! Internet Angel, descending now!
社会をやめろ 家族をやめろ 人間関係をやめろ
Quit society, quit your family, quit human relationships!
今すぐ薄暗い部屋で 青白いライトを浴びろ
Right now, bathe in the pale blue light in a dim room!
大丈夫 こわかったこと全部上書きするからね
It's alright, I'll overwrite everything that scared you.
現実よりも crazy for you
Crazy for you, more than reality!
おかしくなりそうなくらい 情報過多のインターネット
An information-overloaded internet, enough to make you go crazy.
今すぐ助けてあげるよ ダーリン
I'll save you right now, darling,
ダーリン
darling!
ウソはウソで見抜けるし
You can see through lies,
この愛は暴走しちゃうし 壊れてしまうけど
but this love will run wild and break down.
考えなくていいんだよ もうすぐ楽になるから
You don't have to think about it, you'll be at ease soon,
脳内に乱反射する poison radio
Poison radio reflecting chaotically in your brain,
麻薬より甘いよ
sweeter than drugs.
いいねよくないね キミにとっては毒だね
Likes and dislikes, it's poison to you.
いいねよくないね それでも飲むんだね
Likes and dislikes, but you'll still drink it.
いいねよくないね 二人の秘密だね あたしだけ見ててね
Likes and dislikes, our secret, just look at me.
まるで天使のように微笑む
Smiling like an angel,
強めの幻覚 internet girl
a strong hallucination internet girl.
そして悪魔みたいにささやく アナタだけのデパス needy girl
And whispering like a demon, your very own depressant needy girl.
浅い眠りと承認欲求のオーバードーズ
An overdose of shallow sleep and recognition desire,
脳天直撃する わたしたちだけの宗教とヒカリ
a direct hit to our own religion and light.
倫理より激しく生きた 宇宙すら侵食する恋
A love living fiercer than ethics, eroding even the universe.
何度も送られる毒電波を 優しさだけで包んで
Wrapping the poisoned radio waves sent over and over with just kindness.
逆さまのコンピュータと 断片的なカウンセリング
An inverted computer and fragmented counseling,
きらめく屋上で奏でた 夢見心地の旋律
a dreamy melody played on a sparkling rooftop.
夕暮れ時に さよならの練習をして
Practicing saying goodbye at dusk,
壊して愛して許して狂って狂って狂って甘く狂わせて
destroying, loving, forgiving, going mad, driving me sweetly mad.
ゆらぎ始める世界 曖昧になる風景
The world begins to waver, scenery becoming ambiguous,
アナタだけが映っているメモリー
a memory where only you are reflected.
神様なんていないのよ
There's no such thing as God.
このふざけたインターネットは 七色のサイケデリック
This ridiculous internet is a seven-colored psychedelic,
snsという瓶詰め地獄に救済を
bringing salvation to the bottled hell called SNS.
過去の歴史は見ないふり アナタのためならすぐそばに
Turning a blind eye to past history, right by your side if it's for you.
インターネット・エンジェル かわいく参上
Internet Angel making a cute appearance!
まるで天使のように抱きつく 強めの幻覚 internet girl
Hugging you like an angel, a strong hallucination internet girl.
そして悪魔みたいにキスする アナタだけのデパス needy girl
And kissing you like a demon, your very own depressant needy girl.
ANGEL
どうでしたかー！？
How was it?!
すごかったよー！めっちゃ似合うね、そう
It was amazing! It suits you so well, yeah.
だった、だった、だった...
Right, right, right...
めっちゃ頑張っててすごかったし！
You worked really hard and it was amazing!
ありがと！おる？
Thanks! Are you here?
聞こえてるね、あ、そう、ちょっとね
Can you hear us? Ah, yeah, sort of.
ふぶちゃんまじ、そう、かわいい！
Fubuki-chan is seriously, yeah, so cute!
ちょっと次の曲はこの制服で踊りまーす！
Next up, we'll dance to the next song in this uniform!
次の曲はね、ほい、こうね、あのフブちゃん、あ、こうね、選んだんだけど
The next song, like this, um, Fubuki-chan chose it, but
次の曲は、あのね、この可愛いキュートボイスでね
The next song, you know, with this cute voice,
この「ロックンロール」にしてほしい
we wanted it to be "Rock 'n' Roll"...
まさか過ぎる選曲でちょっとびっくりしたけど、でもらしいっちゃらしいっちゃね。
It was such an unexpected song choice that we were a bit surprised, but it suits you in a way.
「ロックンロール」っていう感じの曲はね、歌えはしたけども、やっぱ
The song felt like "Rock 'n' Roll", we managed to sing it, but still...
ころねらしい曲だったな、選曲やっぱ、間違ってなかった
It was a very Korone-like song. The song choice wasn't wrong after all.
息が、息と息がやばい、息が
Our breath, our breathing is crazy, out of breath!
え、近っ！近っ！やめて！
Eh, so close! So close! Stop it!
やめない！やめない！
Won't stop! Won't stop!
あっちでしょ！あっちでしょ！泣かないで、泣かないで！
Over there! Over there! Don't cry, don't cry!
泣くな！泣くな！こっちでしょ！こっち！こっち！
Don't cry! Don't cry! Over here! Here! Here!
だって、私たち「ころねすき」って名前なんだよ？何を捨ててるんだ、泣くな！
After all, our name is "Koronesuki", right? What are you throwing away, don't cry!
ほら、え？え？え？やだ、え？
Look, eh? Eh? Eh? No way, eh?
あ、やだ、え？アンジェ...
Ah, no way, eh? Angel...
え、恥ずかしい、ころね、ころね、やだ！
Eh, how embarrassing, Korone, Korone, no way!
え？え？
Eh? Eh?
え？なんだよ？
Eh? What is it?
なんかお化けみたいなキスしてる！やだ！
It looks like a ghost kissing! No way!
ねぇ、気持ち悪いんだけど！なんで！そうなん...
Hey, it's gross! Why! Is that so...
待って、クリスマス前にそんなことしないで！ころねすきーとして！
Wait, don't do that right before Christmas! As Koronesuki!
はやく帰りなさい、はやく！
Go home quickly, hurry!
帰っちゃうんだね... 何を主張してんねん、それはよ。
You're going home... What are you asserting there, seriously.
大丈夫だから、これでもうじゃあ... あっち行くか。
It's fine, so with that, well... Shall we go over there?
あ、ねぇ、ふぶちゃん！
Ah, hey, Fubuki-chan!
はい、頑張ってね！
Yes, do your best!
頑張るね！ありがとうね！
I'll do my best! Thank you!
いやー、恐ろしいものみたね。
Man, we saw something terrifying.
脳からヒップへ真っ赤に飛び散る
Splatter red from brain to hip,
ファンくなウイルスみたいなオマエ
You like a funk virus.
暴走ボディでキュートな誘惑
Cute temptation...
世界にはびこる憂鬱を壊せ
Break down the melancholy of this world!
世紀末だって過ぎれば昨日さ
Even if the century ends, it's just yesterday.
恋もできないで死ねるわけないだろ
It's not like I can't love and die.
...
容姿は幼で陽気なようでも
Though childish and cheerful in appearance,
酔うと異様に妖艶なヤツ
When drunk, strangely bewitching.
ロリータ・ウイングでキャンディーねだっていざ
With a lolita wink, candy...
娼婦の唇でしゃぶってみろよ
Try sucking on the whore's lips!
世紀末だって過ぎれば昨日さ
Even if the century ends, it's just yesterday.
愛に憑いた悲しみも消える
The sadness of love disappears.
低気圧だって青空の破片
Even low-pressure fragments of blue sky...
キスばら撒いて未来へ行こう
Let's scatter kisses and head to the future!
Don't let me down, my sweet baby BAMBINA
抱きしめたあの夜は秘密さ
That night we embraced was a secret.
ヌードになったら天使の羽根が
When we went nude, angel wings...
バレるぜ BAMBINA
Would be exposed, Bambina!
バンビーナ バンビーナ I love you
Bambina, Bambina, I love you!
キングのルールもギャングのコールも
Neither king's rules nor gang's calls...
今夜のダンスは止められないさ
Tonight's dance cannot be stopped!
ハートのジッパーこっそり開けたら
If you stealthily unzip the heart,
立体映像の夢が飛び出す
A stereoscopic dream leaps out!
世紀末だって過ぎれば昨日さ
Even if the century ends, it's just yesterday.
愛に憑いた悲しみも消える
The sadness of love disappears.
低気圧だって青空の破片
Even low-pressure fragments of blue sky...
キスばら撒いて未来へ行こう
Let's scatter kisses and head to the future!
Don't let me down, my sweet baby BAMBINA
鳥カゴに閉じ込めて逢いたい
Locked in a birdcage, I want to meet you.
退屈するとちゃんと浮気する
When I get bored, I properly cheat.
小悪魔 BAMBINA
A little devil Bambina!
Don't let me down, my sweet baby BAMBINA
抱きしめたあの夜は秘密さ
That night we embraced was a secret.
ヌードになったら天使だったね
When we became nude, you were an angel!
魅惑の BAMBINA
Fascinating Bambina!
バンビーナ バンビーナ I love you
Bambina, Bambina, I love you!
あ、どうも。
Ah, hello!
はい、ということで皆さんでした、ありがとうございます！
All right, everyone, thank you so much!
待て待て待て待て！
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
ころねの、ちょっと待って、待って待って待って！
Hold on, Korone, hold on, hold on, hold on!
おいおい、ちょっと前に並んで、前に並んで！
Hey, hey, hey! Line up in front!
前に並んで！誰が誰？
Line up in front! Who's who?
アイラブユー！
I love you!
待て待て待て待て！
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
待って、待って！それパンツ...
Wait, wait! That's pants...
パンツじゃねえよ！ブルマなんだよ！
It's not pants, it's bloomers!
ほら！あれ今横向いてるのは誰？あなたは？
Wait, look! Why are you facing sideways? Who are you?
コーン！
Corn!
あ、コーン！
Ah, corn!
コーン！コーン！
Corn! Corn!
コーンだよ！
It's corn!
コーンなんか今強気みたいな顔してたけど。
Corn looks all confident right now.
お！
Oh!
怒れる？怒れる？ほら、むってしてむってして。
You can get mad? Can you get mad? Look, mutters...
で、なんかワンワン言ってるのがいるんだけど、これはもしかしてミオ？
And look, everyone's barking, but is this Mio?
うち、うち、うちだよ！
Uchi, uchi, uchi dayo!
なんかこんなんなっちゃった！
Why are you like this?
かわいいね、かわいい、かわいい。
So cute! So cute!
あ、でも戻ってきなさい、あなたたちまったくね！
Hey, come back here, you guys!
ずっとさ、ゆうまんけパンツ見てるでしょ！
You've been looking at bloomers the whole time, right?
バカヤロー戻れ戻れ！
Perverts! Return, return!
変態変態！
Pervert, pervert!
変態じゃないよ！ほら、もとに戻ってきなさいほらほら！
It's not a pervert! Look, return to your original positions!
あっちだよ雪、あっちへまったく！
Go that way, Yuki, go that way, absolutely!
ちゃんと着替えてくるんだよ！
You've gotta change clothes, you know!
ちょっと解除スイッチあるから解除スイッチ、まったく！
There's a changing switch, so use the changing switch, completely!
ほ、どうも、そろそろ戻った？
Well then, have you guys returned yet?
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
まだ。
Not yet.
まだ？いつまで着替えてんだよ！
Not yet? How long are you gonna change?
おかえりおかえり、よかったよかった！
Welcome back, welcome back, welcome back!
なんか見えなくなってる！
You guys became invisible!
いいじゃんそれで、何が問題なんだよ！
It's fine, isn't it? What's wrong with that?
おかゆ、そういう時はな、うん。
Okayu, those moments are...
こう楽しむんだよ！
You gotta get excited, you know!
やばいよ！
No way!
やめなさい！
Don't worry!
なんだったのさ、そのそれちっちゃいとか。
Wait, what was that about being small?
ちっちゃい体どうだったみんな？
How were everyone's small bodies?
楽しかった！
It was fun!
楽しかった？ほんとに？動きづらくなかったか？
It was fun? Honestly, wasn't it hard to move around?
いや、かわいかったよ。
It was cute, though.
ちっちゃくなれるって、あの幸せなことなんだね。
Shrinking... Ah, that's a happy thing, you know.
いや、かわいいだろ、もともと。
Well, it's cute from the start, though.
ということでね、ひととおりね、我々プロデュースした楽曲が終わりましたけども。
So, we've more or less finished the songs we produced, but...
まだまだ歌いますよね、この後もね。
We're still gonna sing more, right? From now on, too!
次は、なんとデュエットということで。
Next is, what, a duet?
どの組み合わせだろう？どことどこが歌うのかな？
Whose combination is it? Which and which will sing?
誰？誰と誰なんだろうね？
Who is it? Who with whom?
かわいい、かわいい、かわいい。
Cute, cute, cute.
でも、その動き見たからさ。
I saw that movement, so...
だめだめだめ、それはだめだ。
That's no good, that's no good, that's no good.
全然いいよ！
It's totally fine, though!
怖いよ！
It's scary!
ダビデの壁、やろっか、こっちも、こうやって。
Shall we do "The Wall of David"? Fubuki, let's do it too, like this.
え、え、え、これどういう意味？アンドウインベダー？
What does this mean? "And then, in bed"?
インべーダー？
In-Invader?
インベーダー？
Invader?
インベーダーってことかな？
Does that mean invader?
まあ、ということで次のね、デュエットの準備をしにみんな行くぞ！
Well then, let's go prepare for the next duet, everyone, let's go!
おー！楽しみにしていてね！行こう！
Let's look forward to it! Let's go!
よいしょ、よいしょ！
Yoisho, yoisho!
チューリングラブ
Turing Love
あー、恋の定義がわかんない
Ah, the definition of love is a mystery.
まずスキって基準もわかんない
First of all, I don't even know what "like" is based on.
要は、恋してる時が恋しい
The point is, when you're in love, that's when it's lovely.
客観？ 主観？ エビデンスプリーズ！
Objective? Subjective? Evidence Please!
愛は計算じゃ解けない
Love cannot be solved by calculations.
まず普通の計算も解けない
In fact, normal calculations can't be solved either.
要はそんな状態が愛らしい
The point is, that state of being is adorable.
アイノウ？ 大抵の事象においてはQがあってAを出して解けるのに
Ain't you? Most of the time, Q comes up and A comes out, and you can solve it, but...
勘違いって間違って解いのないこの気持ちはなんだろう (検証is不明瞭)
Miscalculated, misunderstood, what on earth is this feeling with no answer? (Verification is unclear)
DAZING!! モーションは相対性にステイ
DAZING!! Motion stays relative.
チューリングラブ 見つめあったって解けないメロウ
Turing Love: A melody where looking at each other isn't enough to solve it.
ホワットイズラブ いま123で証そうか
What is Love? Let's prove it now with 1, 2, 3.
言葉で生み出すクエスト (クエスト!)
A quest born from words (Quest!)
ハートで高鳴るアンサー (アンサー!)
An answer that beats in the heart (Answer!)
測ったって不確定性 ぼくらのBPM
Measured and full of uncertainty, our BPM.
チューリングラブ 宙に舞ったって信じないけど
Turing Love: Even if we dance through the skies, I can't believe it.
フォーリンラブ いまはABCすらバグりそうた
Falling Love: Right now, even ABCs seem like they're gonna bug out.
なんでか教えてオイラ (オイラ!)
Tell me why, Oila! (Oila!)
感想聞かせてフェルマー (フェルマー!)
Let me hear your thoughts, felmer! (Felmer!)
予測不可能性 いま触れてみる
Unpredictability, let's touch it right now.
さあ証明しよう (証明しよう) 間違いのないように
Let's prove it! (Prove it!) So there's no mistake.
証明しよう (証明しよう) この感情全部全部
Let's prove it! (Prove it!) All of this emotion.
証明しよう (証明しよう) 正解があるなら
Let's prove it! (Prove it!) If there is a correct answer.
証明しよう (証明しよう) シンプルなQ.E.D.
Let's prove it! (Prove it!) A simple Q.E.D.
今日こそ証明したいよ (証明したいよ)
Today, I want to prove it! (Prove it!)
目に見えない 無理難題を
Invisible, impossible problems.
ASAP!
導き出したい たどり着きたい 最適解へ
I want to derive it, reach it, to the optimal solution.
何度から回ったって ぶつかっちゃったって
No matter how many times we spin, no matter how many times we collide.
不思議なこのアノマリーを 解き明かす過程さえ 必須条件です
Solving this mysterious anomaly is a prerequisite.
3次元 (立体) における2点AB間の距離を求めよ
"Find the distance between two points AB in 3D (solid) space."
的な感じだと思ってたのに
I thought it was that kind of feeling, but...
座標も公式も見当たらないし
Neither coordinates nor formulas are to be found anywhere.
参考資料にも載っていないから 君と生み出してみせたいじゃん
They aren't even in the reference materials, so let's bring them to life with you!
3次元 (世界) における この気持ちの求め方
How to figure out this feeling in 3D (world) space.
丸だってバツだって不安にとってイコールで 近くなって遠くなって揺れるこの気持ちの針も
Getting closer, getting further away, the needle of this swaying feeling...
条件is明瞭
Condition is clear.
Steppin'!!
エモーションは相愛性ミステイク
Emotions are relative mistakes!
チューリングラブ 騒ぎ出した胸の痛くなるほど
Turing Love! My chest aches so much from the commotion,
証明は今も角度を増しているようだ
Even now, the proof seems to be gaining angles.
曖昧も除外して
Excluding ambiguity,
最大の仮説を
our greatest hypothesis—
いま、ふたりなら実証できそう
right now, the two of us can prove it!
チューリングラブ 見つめあったってきりないメロウ
Turing Love! Melodies are endless when we gaze at each other,
ワットイズラブ いま123で明かそうか
What is Love? Shall we reveal it in 1, 2, 3?
言葉で生み出すクエスチョン ハートで高鳴るアンサー
Questions born from words, answers echoing in our hearts!
測ったって不確定性 ぼくらのBPM
Measured yet uncertain, that's our BPM!
チューリングラブ 宙に舞ったってその因果も
Turing Love! Dancing in the air, even that causality—
フォーリンラブ いまはXYZまで分かりそうだ
Fall in Love! Now we might even understand up to XYZ!
確かめさせてピタゴラス
Let us confirm it, Pythagoras!
確かにさせてよリーマン
Let's make it certain, Riemann!
予測済み可変性 いま触れてみる
Pre-predicted variability, let's touch it now!
さあ証明しよう
Now, let's prove it!
間違いのないように証明しよう
Let's prove it without any mistakes!
この感情全部全部証明しよう
Let's prove all, all of these emotions!
世界があるなら証明しよう
If the world exists, let's prove it!
推測を超えて！証明しよう
Surpassing estimations, let's prove it!
間違いのないように証明しよう
Let's prove it without any mistakes!
この感情全部全部証明しよう
Let's prove all, all of these emotions!
世界があるなら証明しよう
If the world exists, let's prove it!
シンプルなQ.E.D.
A simple Q.E.D.!
L R L R STOP & DASH & UP & TALK B B A B S(tart)
これがわたしをリモートコントロールする機械です
This is a machine that remote controls me.
少し歪な形しておりますが、使えます。
It's shaped a bit weirdly, but it works.
UP SIDE DOWN A B A B B A B A 左右
UP SIDE DOWN A B A B B A B A left-right
L R L R STOP & DASH & UP & TALK 異常ナシ
L R L R STOP & DASH & UP & TALK No anomalies!
もうちょっとで外に出られるのにな
Even though I could go outside a little more...
どうやってうまくいかないね
It just won't go well no matter what.
まだまだ足りない
Still, still not enough!
座る 座る SIT DOWN PLEASE
Sit down, sit down, sit down please!
フィードバックに体預けて 巡る 巡る TURN IT AROUND
Entrusting my body to feedback, turning around and around!
うなりを上げて モータ状態
Raising a roar, motor status active!
踊る 踊る DANCIN' NIGHT
Dancing, dancing, dancin' night!
マッシュアップでもれなくアガル
Soaring without fail in the mashup!
声を上げて SINGIN' NOW
Raising our voices, singin' now!
あの子よりもうまく歌いたい
I want to sing better than that girl!
これがボクをリモートで操縦できる機械です。
This is a machine that remote controls me.
説明書は紛失しておりますが使えます。
The manual is missing, but it works.
UP SIDE DOWN A B A B B A B A 左右
UP SIDE DOWN A B A B B A B A left-right
L R L R STOP & DASH & UP & TALK 異常ナシ
L R L R STOP & DASH & UP & TALK No anomalies!
からかってるみたいないつもの顔
That usual teasing-like face—
今日はかなり本気だぜ ほらすぐキメるぜ
today I'm quite serious! Come on, let's nail it right away!
座る 座る SIT DOWN PLEASE
Sit down, sit down, sit down please!
トークバックを頭に挿して 回る 回る
Sticking the talkback on my head, spinning round and round!
TURN IT AROUND
ちょっと待ってスタンバイ状態 踊る 踊る DANCIN' NIGHT
Wait a second, standby mode! Dancing, dancing, dancin' night!
ジャストフィットなリズムを出して 唸り上げる SINGIN' NOW
Delivering a just-fit rhythm, raising a roar, singin' now!
アイツよりも高く歌いたい
I want to sing higher than that guy!
惚れたはれたの七色侍
The seven-color samurai, falling in and out of love,
洗いさらえ主張する存在 思い違いが透けてるアンバイ
making bold assertions, showing mismatched feelings—
怖いくらい
so scary...
惚れた腫れたの七色侍
Infatuations of all seven colors,
洗いざらい主張する存在
A completely assertive existence.
思い違いが透けてるアンビバ
Transparently mistaken ambivalence,
怖いぐらいのwktk状態
A frighteningly excited state.
気にしないのがあなたのポリシー?
Is it your policy not to care?
悩んでいてもお腹は減るし
Even when worried, I get hungry.
なんだかんだで世間はヘルシー
Somehow, the world is healthy.
おきをたしかにぬるま湯ダンシ!
Pull yourself together, lukewarm boy!
もうちょっとでスキマ埋まるのにな
The gap's almost filled, but...
どうやってもうまくいかね。
No matter what, it doesn't go well.
ああ もう時間が 足りない
Ah, there's already no time left.
座る座る sit down please
Sit down, sit down, sit down please!
フィードバックに体預けて
Entrusting my body to the feedback,
廻る廻る turn it around
Spin around, spin around, turn it around!
頷きを上げて、モーター状態
Nodding high in motor state.
踊る踊る dancin' night
Dance, dance, dancin' night!
マッシュアップでもれなくアガる!
Exhilaratingly rising with a mashup!
声をあげて singin' now
Raise your voice, singin' now!
あの子みたいなヒトになりたい
I want to be like that girl.
座る座る sit down please
Sit down, sit down, sit down please!
廻る廻る turn it around
Spin around, spin around, turn it around!
踊る踊る dancin' night
Dance, dance, dancin' night!
声をあげて singin' now
Raise your voice, singin' now!
あの子みたいなヒトになりたい
I want to be like that girl.
げまどんでレード!!!!
Gamers' Raid!!!!
最後どうなってんのあれ
How did that end?
そうだよ
That's right.
わかんない、あれどうなったんだろうね
I don't know, how did it end up?
あれはちょっとね、あの、ご想像にお任せします
Well, that's... I'll leave that to your imagination.
じゃあいいのね、いろんな想像したいいのね
So anything goes? Any imagination is fine!
逆にね！どんな想像するんだよ！でもリモコンもめちゃめちゃよかった
On the contrary! What kind of imagination?! But Remote Control was super good too!
よかった！
It was good!
最後まで言えなかった
I couldn't say it to the end.
難しいよね！早口頑張ったよね！
It's hard! You worked hard on the fast part!
さてさてまだまだですね、もうちょっとだけゲーマーズの続くんですけども
Now then, there's still more, Gamers continues a bit longer, but...
そろそろちょっとグッズの告知をしようかと
It's about time to announce some merchandise.
グッズ出るんですか！？グッズでございまーす！告知です！こちらご覧ください！
Merchandise is coming out?! It's merchandise! Here's the announcement! Please take a look!
ホロライブゲーマーズ6周年記念グッズでーす！
Hololive Gamers 6th Anniversary merchandise!
わーい！わーい！
Yay! Yay!
ということで、まずはひとつめこちらー！
So, first up is this one!
あ、こちら！アクリルスタンドでーす！
Ah, here! Acrylic stands!
かわいい！こちらオットン先生に描き下ろしていただきました！
So cute! Drawn by Oton-sensei!
今回はね、あの、我々はサイバーでゲーマーな感じということで、で、あのアイドル感も忘れない、すさまじい
This time, we have a cyber, gamer vibe, while not forgetting the idol feel—amazing!
イラストの中、あの、衣装もね、新期の、そうそうそう新しい衣装を作ってもらったんだよね！
In the illustration, the outfits are brand new! They made us brand new outfits!
俺めちゃめちゃかわいいですよね！
We look super cute, right?
ただ次もありますよ、こちらちょっと次も、バーンと。
There's more! Next up, bam!
今回のライブステージをイメージした大型パーツもついていますので、4人並べると大迫力で楽しめます！
It comes with large parts inspired by this live stage, so lining up all four makes it super powerful!
完璧に4つ揃えたらね、いい、是非是非飾ってください！
If you collect all four perfectly, please decorate with them!
では続いて、2つ目こちら！カードスリーブ！
Next, the second item, here! Card sleeves!
これあれだ、サムネでも...
Is this also in the thumbnail...?
そうなんです！さかなへん先生に描いていただきました！
That's right! Drawn by Sakanahen-sensei!
カードスリーブ、一般的なカードが入るサイズとなっておりますので、使い勝手抜群でございます！
Card sleeves fit standard card sizes, so they're super practical!
60枚も入ってるのか！しかもホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームのカードも入ります！
60 cards included! And Hololive Official Card Game cards fit too!
さすが生徒！最近さかなへんでいっぱい出てるもんね！ぜひぜひ好きに使ってください！
As expected! They've been coming out a lot lately! Please use them as you like!
では続いて、3つ目こちら！ラバーマット！
And next, the third item, here! Rubber mat!
これスリーブとおそろっちとなっております！ゲーマーズ好きな人はたまらんよね！
This matches the sleeves! Gamers fans won't be able to resist!
ぜひぜひラバーマットもゲーマーズで使っていただきたいです！対戦でもぜひぜひご利用ください！
Please use the rubber mat for Gamers stuff too! Please use it in matches as well!
よろしくお願いします。
Please look forward to it.
ほしぃよね。我々ほしいねえさんください。
We want it! Give us some, Fubuki-neesan.
お願いします! 送ってください。
Please! Send us some!
送ってください。
Send us some!
そして4つ目は、こちら!
And the fourth item is right here!
ジャーン! キャップ!
Ta-da! A cap!
わあー!
Wow!
これさあ、ロゴがね、我々のこれ入ってるんですけども
This has our logo on it,
うちわのこと、うちわのことじゃなくてスモックならぬフモックが入ってるんですよ。
but instead of "Uchiwa," it actually says "Fumock"—like a smock!
本当だ!
That's right!
あれ? なんか… スモックになってます。
Wait... it's a smock design!
そこはゲーマーズでよかったのではと、あともう思ったよ。
I thought it should've just been "Gamers," but whatever.
なんでフモックになってるの? そうそうそうそう!
Why is it "Fumock"? Exactly, right!
これあの、スモック好きな方はあの、FSにしてください。
If you really love smocks, make it FS.
なんで、そんなことないじゃん! なんてこと言うの! なんてこと言うの!
What, that's not true! Why would you say that?!
めちゃくちゃ言わないでください!
Don't say such terrible things!
はい、お願いします。
Okay, please.
言わないで! 言わないでください!
Don't say it! Please don't say that!
はい、これ横にねコントローラーもついてるのでね、本当に我々ゲーマーズらしいキャップとなっております。
Yeah, it even has a controller on the side, making it a cap that truly fits us Gamers.
耳入るかな?
Will our ears fit?
うちら、うちらはちょっと厳しいかもしれない。
Well, for us, it might be a bit tough.
ちょっとね、潰さないといけない。
Yeah, we'd have to squash them down.
コルネは、コロンねはギリ入る。コーリタンはもう潰れてるからもう。
Korone—well, Korone barely fits. Korone's are already squashed anyway.
潰せば、潰せばいい。耳は、耳ティッシュだから大丈夫。
If you squash them, it's fine. Our ears are made of tissue, so it's fine!
痛いよ絶対。
That's definitely gonna hurt!
と、いうことで、最後はこちらでございます。
And with that, here is our final item.
ブロマイドケース!
A bromide case!
おお! すごい!
Oh! Awesome!
かわいい!
So cute!
今回のサムネイルを使ったブロマイドと、我々からの複製メッセージが入っております。
It comes with a bromide using our thumbnail and duplicated messages from us!
ね、中身が届いてからのお楽しみとなっておりますので、ぜひ手に入れて確認してください。
It'll be a surprise once you receive it, so please get yours and check it out!
いいね、なんて書いてるかな。
Nice, wonder what it says.
なんで書いたっけ。
What did I write again?
忘れちゃった。忘れちゃった。
I forgot! I forgot!
ファンのみんなに書いたよ。
I wrote it for all the fans!
嘘、ファンのみんなに当てたやないかい!
No way, you wrote it for the fans, didn't you!
じゃあみんな教えてね。
Then everyone, tell us.
教えてね。
Tell us!
ということで、グッズのご紹介は、こちらで以上でございます。
And that wraps up the merchandise introduction.
ありがたき幸せだね。
We're so grateful.
ね、今回ですね、フルセットの販売がございませんので、
Now, since there won't be a full set for sale this time,
欲しいものを単体で、ご購入ください。
please purchase the items you want individually.
お願いします。
Please do!
はい、数量限定もの、そう、あるね。
Yes, and as for the limited quantity items...
そうなんです、数量限定ものないので、あの、じっくりじっくり、あの考えてたくさんお迎えしてくれると嬉しいです。
there's no strict quantity limit, so please take your time to think about it and get as many as you like!
はい、お願いします。
Yes, please!
でもきっと受注期間はあるよね。
But I'm sure there's an ordering period, right?
ま、さすがにあると思います。
Yeah, I'm sure there is.
さすがにではないかな。詳細はグッズ販売ページからご確認をお願いします。
But just to be sure, please check the merch page for details.
お願いします。お願いします。
Please check it out!
そしてそして、ちょっと個人的な告知が白神もございます。
And now, Fubuki has a personal announcement to make.
おお、なんだなんだ?
Oh, what is it?
はい!
Yes!
え、ありがたいことに2025年2月13日に、白神フブキソロライブ「FBKINGDOM ANTHEM」がPIA ARENA MMにて開催でございます!
Thanks to you all, Fubuki Shirakami's solo live "FBKINGDOM ANTHEM" will be held at Pia Arena MM on February 13, 2025!
おめでとう! おめでとう!
Congratulations! Congratulations!
ただね、あの昨日ゲストの告知もしまして、みこメットが来てくれることになりました。
Also, we announced our guests yesterday, and Miko-met will be joining us!
ありがたい!
Thank you so much!
え、こちらはですね、二次先行のあの、お申し込みがですね、あの明日、明日の23時59分となっておりますので、よろしくお願いいたします。
As for ticket pre-orders, the second round closes tomorrow at 23:59, so please apply!
明日開始なの、二次先行?
Tomorrow's the deadline for the second pre-order?
明日終わり。
Tomorrow's the end.
終わりなの!?
It's ending?!
じゃあ今すぐやったほうがいい。はい、よろしくお願いいたします。
Then you better do it right now! Yes, please do!
よろしくお願いいたします。
Please check it out!
ということで、ライブももう終盤でございますね。
And with that, the live is reaching its final stretch.
あと、あと一曲?
Just one more song left?
え、もう終わり? あと一曲残してんのか。
Huh, already? We have one song left.
そうなんだよ。逆にね、逆にね。
That's right. Actually, quite the opposite.
あれ? でも、なんかまだ歌ってないや、歌ってないや。
Huh? But it feels like we haven't sung enough yet.
ありますね。ま、なんですけども。
True. But anyway...
ちょっとね、改めて我々今回6周年を迎えたということで、それぞれ一言ずつね。
Now, since we just celebrated our 6th anniversary, let's each say a few words.
まあ、今まで振り返りでもいいし、また来年に向けてでもいいので、一言ずつはちょっとミオからいいですか?
You can look back on the past or talk about next year. Mio, can you start?
うちからですか? はい、はい。
Us? Okay, okay.
どうでした?
How was it?
うちは2024年はゲーマーズのね、イベントとかね、あったのにさ。
For me, 2024 had all these Gamers events and stuff,
うちは出れなかったっていうこととかあったので、ちょっと悲しい年になってしまったんですけど
but I wasn't able to participate in some, so it became a bit of a sad year for me.
2025年はゲーマーズのみんなと一緒に最高の年にしたいなって思っているのね。
But for 2025, I want to make it the absolute best year together with all the Gamers members!
頑張って健康的に過ごしたいなって思ってます。はい。よろしくね、みんなにね。
I want to work hard and stay healthy. Yeah, looking forward to it, everyone.
いや、よろしくお願いいたします。
Yes, looking forward to it.
はい、そして、じゃあフブキ。はいはい。
And now, Fubuki. Okay.
白上もね、2024年はあの、ちょこちょこちょこちょこゲーマーズもね、ありましてね。
For Fubuki, in 2024, we had various Gamers activities here and there.
でもと残念ながらね、みおが参加できなかったので、ま、来年、再来年とかを目指してね、このゲーマーズでまた頑張ってちょこちょこちょこちょこゲーマーズ2をね、開催できるようにしていきます。
Unfortunately, Mio couldn't join us, so looking towards next year and beyond, I want us Gamers to work hard so we can hold "Cho-Cho-Cho-Cho Gamers 2"!
いや、やりたくないってだって!
Hey, she said she doesn't want to do it!
やりたいけど、そんな簡単にやろうって言ってできるようなもんじゃないからさ。
I want to, but it's not something you can just easily put together!
やらせてください!
Please let us do it!
お願いします。よろしくお願いします。
Please! We're counting on you.
頑張ります。頑張ります。まあ、オンラインはね、今日あれとしてオフラインをまた目指して、頑張っていきたいと思います。
We'll do our best. Today is online, but we'll aim for an offline one next and do our best!
おめでとう! おめでとう! おめでとう!
Congratulations! Congratulations! Congratulations!
さてさてじゃあ続いておかゆん。
Now then, Okayu.
いやあ、もう6周年ですか。早いですね。
Man, 6 years already. Time flies.
早いですよね。早いよね。
It really does. It really does.
そんな気する?
Do you feel that way?
しない。
Not really!
じゃあ、まだだ。
Then we're just getting started!
1年目くらいの気持ちでいるけどね、やっぱ新人、新人。
I feel like it's our first year, but we're still total newbies.
そうだよね、まだまだ気持ちは新人、初心を忘れずにね。
That's right, we're still newbies at heart. We mustn't forget our roots.
さあ、頑張っていきたいと思ってますよ、やっぱり、本部に抱っこしてくださいって感じだよね。
So yeah, we want to keep doing our best, like "please hold us in HQ."
本部に抱っこ？どういうこと？
Hold you in HQ? What does that mean?
おかころでってこと？おかころ本部抱っこなの？
You mean OkaKoro? Is OkaKoro being held by HQ?
え、おかころ背負えるの？
Eh, can you carry OkaKoro?
うえー！
Whoa!
後で試そう、後で。
Let's try it later, later.
物理的なんだね、なるほどね。
So it's physical, I see.
まあでもみおちゃんも言ってましたけど、みんなでね、また楽しいゲマズ生活を送りたいと
Well, Mio-chan also said it, but we want to have another fun Gamers life together with everyone...
思っておりますよ！2025年も楽しい1年にしようね！
We really think so! Let's make 2025 a fun year too!
で、ゲマズとはまた遊びたい！わーいじゃあ、遊びたい！
And, we want to play with Gamers again! Yay, then we want to play!
だから、ゲマズさ、最近さ、コラ多くないよね？
That's why, Gamers, lately there's a lot of collab, right?
前は1年に1回集まれればいいほうだったのにさ。
Before, getting together once a year was already a lot.
ちょっと増えてきたよね。
It's increased a bit.
確かに、確かに。
True, true.
え、裏ある？なんか。
Eh, is there a secret agenda? Something.
裏ってどういうこと？
What do you mean by secret agenda?
え、だってお金ってさ、なんか、あるの？お金ない？何、裏ってなんなんだよ？裏表ないの？大丈夫なの？
Eh, because money... is there something? No money? What, what's a secret agenda? Isn't there two sides? Is it okay?
いや、普通に仲良くしてるだけだよね？そうそう、仲良く。
No, we're just getting along normally, right? Yeah, getting along.
裏なんかさ、ないよ！
There's no secret agenda!
裏なんてさ、ないよ！何の裏だよ！見落としっぱなしだったら死ねだろ！
There's no secret agenda! What kind of agenda?! If we missed something we'd die!
失礼しました！
Excuse me!
で、結局、結局何が言いたいんだよ？
So, in the end, what are you trying to say?
来年も仲良く4人で活動していきましょう！やったー！来年も！4人で仲良く活動していきましょう！イエーイ！
Let's keep happily doing activities together as four next year too! Yay! Let's happily do activities together as four next year too! Yay!
素晴らしい！素晴らしい！そしてプラスリスナーさんもね！あ、そうだね！
Wonderful! Wonderful! And the listeners too! Ah, that's right!
これからもね、ホロライブゲマズ、ファンの皆さんとともどもね、よろしくお願いいたします！よろしくお願いいたします！
From now on as well, Hololive Gamers, along with all the fans, please treat us well! Please treat us well!
さて、じゃあもうみんな言い残すことはないかい？
Now then, does anyone have anything left unsaid?
大丈夫？ない！痛い痛い痛い！
Are you okay? None! It hurts, hurts, hurts!
最後の1曲、行っちゃいますよ！はい！
We'll go with the final song! Yes!
ということでね、今回まだライブで使っていない前のステージに行って、おきがえもして、みんなで歌いたいと思います！
And so, we'll go to the previous stage we haven't used in this live yet, change our clothes, and sing together!
ということで行くぞステージ！イエーイ！
And so, off to the stage! Yay!
We are GAMERS!!!!
こーん！とキツネが登場 白髪ケモミミ白上フブキです
Con! A fox appears. White hair, kemomimi, Shirakami Fubuki here!
スッ込んじゃって始まらない 君もスコン部にいんぷしなさい
It won't start if you hide away. Why don't you join the Sukon-bu too?
Hi Friends! (Yeah!) Hi Friends! (Yeah!)
古今東西コーン茶をごちーょだい
Give me corn tea from past and present, please!
AIじゃないし得意はMC
I'm not an AI, my specialty is MC.
赤い恋より金の鯉が推し♡
Instead of red love, gold carp is my oshi!
うちうちうちだよ大神ミオだよ 黒髪ケモミミ狼（みおーん！）
It's me, Ookami Mio! Black hair, kemomimi wolf (Mio-n!)
ツッコんで止めます Like a ママ
I stop you with a tsukkomi, Like a Mama.
笑い出すと止まらないゲラゲラ
Once I start laughing it won't stop, cackle cackle.
つまり実はPONってコト？！
Meaning actually, it means PON?!
小足ステップしちゃう音
Small foot step sound.
タロット占いで見る未来 ホラーゲームはやりたくなァい！
The future seen through tarot reading: I don't wanna play horror games!
4人揃えばゲマズ最強
When four gather, Gamers are the strongest!
君も遊ぼうよバッドダッシュ
Come play with us too, bad dash!
クリア目指してレベル上げ
Raise your level aiming for a clear.
今日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today?
君のハートも攻略しちゃうぜ 選択をしてシミュレーション
We'll攻略 your heart too. Make a choice and simulate!
初見も古参も対よろ
Nice to meet you, newbies and veterans alike!
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
Games are really fun, aren't they?
We are GAMERS!!!!
いっくよーもぐもぐー 猫又おかゆ おにぎりおにぎりはいどうもー
Here we go, mogu-mogu~ Nekomata Okayu, onigiri onigiri, hi everyone!
キラキラフラフラショーない猫だもん
Sparkling, flitting, a helpless cat.
ふーんそっか 僕でよくない？
Hmm, is that so? Isn't me fine?
まったりゆっくり跳ねるリズム 全肯定するおかゆイズム
Relaxed and slow, bouncing rhythm. Okayuism that totally affirms everything.
全行程効率OK 毎日僕とい〜っしょ！
All processes efficient OK. Every day together with me!
おあっよーゆびゆびわんわん
Oha-yo yubi-yubi wan-wan!
パンをコネコネ戌神ころね
Kneading bread, Inugami Korone.
犬種：キャバリア・キング・チャールズ・スパニエル 懐くけど圧かける
Dog breed: Cavalier King Charles Spaniel. Friendly, but applies pressure.
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are GAMERS!!!!
こーん！とキツネが 登場
Koon! With a fox popping in,
白髪ケモミミ 白上フブキです
Shirakami Fubuki is here, the white-haired kemonomimi!
スッ入んないと 始まらない
Without diving right in, nothing starts,
君もすこん部に 入部し なさい
So you gotta join the "Sokon" club too!
Hi friends!
(Yeah!)
古今東西 コーン茶を ちょーだい
A dash of green tea from East and West, ancient and modern,
AIじゃないし 得意はMC
Not AI, but good at MCs,
赤い恋より 金の鯉が 推し
Simping for golden carp rather than red romance!
うち うち うちだよ 大神ミオだよ
That's us, that's us, Ookami Mio!
黒髪ケモミミ 狼 (みおーん！)
Black-haired kemonomimi wolf, (Myoon!)
4人揃えば ゲーマーズ最強
When all four gather, Gamers are the strongest!
君も遊ぼうよ Bダッシュ
Come play with us too, B-Dash!
クリア目指し てレベル上げ
Aiming to clear, raise that level!
今日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today?
君のハートも 攻略しちゃう
We'll even conquer your heart!
選択をして シミュレーション
Make your choices and simulate,
初見も古参も 対よろ
First-timers and veterans alike, look forward to it!
やっぱりゲームは 楽しいね
After all, games are so much fun!
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are GAMERS!!!!
いっくよー もぐもぐ～ 猫又おかゆ
Here we go, Mogu Mogu! Nekomata Okayu!
おにぎり おにぎりは いづうぜー
Rice balls, rice balls, always ready!
きらきら ふらふら しゃ～ない猫だもん
Sparkling, fluttering, a cat who won't do it!
ふーん そっかぁ 僕でよくない？
Humpfh, I wonder, isn't it fine with just me?
まったり ゆっくり 跳ねる リズム
Mellow, leisurely, bouncing rhythm,
全肯定する おかゆイズム
Okayu-ism of total affirmation!
全行程効率 OK
Efficiency in all processes OK,
毎日僕といーっしょ！
Every day is play-with-me day!
おぁょー ゆびゆび ワンワン
A-hey! Yubi Yubi! Bow-wow!
パンをコネコネ 疫神ころね
Kneading bread, shaking the God of pestilence,
犬種：キャバリア・キング・チャールズ・スパニエル
Dog breed: Cavalier King Charles Spaniel,
懐くけど 圧かける
Affectionate yet overwhelming!
訊る イントネーション
Shrill intonation,
割れる リアクション
Splitting reaction,
まずは指を 捧げてくれる？ 配信ショー
First, can you offer a finger? A broadcast show!
わかったなーぼーね 指示厨おけ
"Got it, na-bo-ne," instructions accepted!
好物のレトロゲー お届け
Delivering my favorite retro games!
4人揃えば ゲーマーズ最高
When all four gather, Gamers are the greatest!
フラグが立てば すぐ回収
If a flag goes up, collect it immediately!
エイム鍛えて 狙い撃ち
Train your aim and snipe away!
今日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today?
君のハートも 回復しちゃう
We'll even recover your heart!
ワクワクするね このダンジョン
This dungeon makes us so excited!
“耐久”っていうか 止められない
Not so much endurance, but we can't stop!
だってゲームが 好きなんだもん
Because we just love games!
「突然ですが、ボーナスチャレンジの時間です。
"Suddenly, it's bonus challenge time!
大きな声でレスポンスをして 高得点を狙いましょう (`・ω・´)」
Let's do a loud response and aim for a high score! (`・ω・´)"
Say!! こーんこーんっ！ (こーんこーんっ！)
Say!! Koon-koon! (Koon-koon!)
Say!! みおーんみおーんっ！ (みおーんみおーんっ！)
Say!! Myoon-myoon! (Myoon-myoon!)
Say!! もぐもぐっ！ (もぐもぐっ！)
Say!! Mogu-mogu! (Mogu-mogu!)
Say!! ゆびゆびっ！ (ゆびゆびっ！)
Say!! Yubi-yubi! (Yubi-yubi!)
Say!! こーんこーんっ！ (こーんこーんっ！)
Say!! Koon-koon! (Koon-koon!)
Say!! みおーんみおーんっ！ (みおーんみおーんっ！)
Say!! Myoon-myoon! (Myoon-myoon!)
Say!! もぐもぐっ！ (もぐもぐっ！)
Say!! Mogu-mogu! (Mogu-mogu!)
Say!! ゆびゆびっ！ (ゆびゆびっ！)
Say!! Yubi-yubi! (Yubi-yubi!)
(Perfect!!) ゲーマーズ「おぁ～!!!!」
(Perfect!!) Gamers: "Ohhhhh!!!!"
4人揃えば ゲーマーズ最強
When all four gather, Gamers are the strongest!
上手く行かなくても コンティニュー
Even if things don't go well, continue!
全クリアするまで 諦めない
Don't give up until you clear it all,
エンディングを見に行こう
Let's go see the ending!
君のハートも 攻略しちゃう
We'll even conquer your heart!
選択をして シミュレーション
Select and simulate,
初見も古参も 対よろ
First-timers and veterans alike, look forward to it!
やっぱりゲームは 楽しいね
After all, games are so much fun!
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are GAMERS!!!!
こうして世界に 平和が訪れたのであった―
And thus, peace came to the world—